thehundreds.com 2019-03-30

# Privacy Policy – The Hundreds

This Privacy Policy is provided to explain how information is collected on our website and how that information is handled once it has been collected. This Privacy Policy may change at any time. By using the thehundreds.com website, you accept the terms and conditions outlined in this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use.

### THE KIND OF INFORMATION COLLECTED

There are cases where The Hundreds may ask you for personal information, such as your name, address, telephone number, date of birth, email address, payment information, etc. We may do this for instance when you make a purchase through the Online Shop, respond to communications such as email, or for services that require registration such as to be included on our mailing list. However, if you would like to be on our mailing list, we will ask you to opt-in. We might also collect personal information from you about a third party, for instance if you ask us to ship product to a third party we may ask for the name, e-mail address, address, phone number, etc. of the recipient. That information will only be used for the specific purpose for which the information was provided and The Hundreds will not further contact the third party unless the third party contacts us.

We may use “cookies” to gather information about your visits to our website and to enhance your experience. Cookies are small text files that are stored on your computer’s hard drive and used by thehundreds.com to enhance your shopping experience by speeding up the browsing experience and website performance. Cookies also are used to personalize your experience while using the thehundreds.com website and remembering your information when you return to the thehundreds.com website. You can turn off all cookies, in case you prefer not to receive them. You also can have your computer warn you whenever cookies are being used. For both options you have to adjust your browser settings (e.g. internet explorer; firefox). Please not that when you have set your computer to reject cookies, it can limit the functionality of the website you visit and it’s possible that you do not have access to some of the features on the website.

We may collect “click stream” data (e.g. server address, domain name, etc.) and demographic or 3rd-party audience data (such as age, gender and interests) with Google Analytics to better understand our audience. This information may be combined with information you have provided to us thereby enabling us to enhance your experience.

### USE OF INFORMATION

All personal information that we obtain about you will be recorded, used, and protected by us in accordance with current data protection legislation and this Privacy Policy. We primarily will use your personal information to provide products and services to you (e.g. to process and ship your online order). Thehundreds.com periodically will update customers via email about new product updates and promotions. If you wish to be removed from this email list, then please visit thehundreds.com and remove your email address by updating your personal information or click the “safeunsubscribe” link at the bottom of an email you have received from us. (To update your personal information via the website, log onto thehundreds.com and click “My Account.” If you have lost or do not remember your password, then please send an email from the email address you used to register your account. We will only send password information to the email address listed under the account. Password information will not be given out over the phone.)

Except as described in this Privacy Policy, we do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer your personal information to third parties without informing you in advance and in accordance with applicable data protection law. Your data may be transferred to web site hosting partners and other parties who assist us in designing and operating the website, executing services, or analyzing collected data. These parties only will use your data for the purpose of carrying out the word as indicated and will be required to keep the information confidential. We also will release personal data without consent if such is required by law or for security purposes.

By using our website, you (the visitor) agree to allow third parties to process your IP address, in order to determine your location for the purpose of currency conversion. You also agree to have that currency stored in a session cookie in your browser (a temporary cookie which gets automatically removed when you close your browser). We do this in order for the selected currency to remain selected and consistent when browsing our website so that the prices can convert to your (the visitor) local currency.

### SECURITY OF INFORMATION

The security of the information you provide to us is protected by various security measures we have implemented. Your personal information is maintained through secure networks and is only accessible by a limited number of people who have special access rights and are required to keep the information confidential. Notwithstanding thehundreds.com’s efforts, no transmission of data over the Internet is guaranteed to be completely secure and such transmission is at your own risk.

### LINKS TO THIRD PARTIES

For your convenience and to improve the usage of the website, we insert links to third parties, for which this Privacy Policy does not apply. These links take you outside our services and off the thehundreds.com website and are beyond our control. This includes links from parties that may use The Hundreds logos as part of a co-branding agreement or sell The Hundreds’ products. The sites you can link to have their own separate Privacy Policy and although we seek to protect the integrity of our site, The Hundreds is not responsible and cannot be held liable for the content and activities of these sites. Your visit/access to these sites therefore is entirely at your own risk. Please note that these other sites may send their own cookies to users, collect data or solicit personal information.

### YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS

California Civil Code Section 1798.83 et. seq. permits customers of The Hundreds who are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please write to us at the following address: The Hundreds is Huge, Inc., 3150 E. 46th Street, Vernon, CA 90058, Attn: General Counsel. In your request, please specify that you want a “California Privacy Rights Notice.” Please allow up to 30 days for a response.

### LIMITATION ON LIABILITY

IN NO EVENT SHALL THE HUNDREDS, ANY OF THE HUNDREDS’ AFFILLIATES, OR ANY OF THEIR OWNERS, OFFICERS, DIRECTORS, EMPLOYEES, OR AGENTS BE LIABLE FOR ANY INDIRECT, SPECIAL, PUNITIVE, INCIDENTAL, EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES, WHETHER IN AN ACTION UNDER CONTRACT, NEGLIGENCE OR ANY OTHER THEORY, ARISING FROM OR IN CONNECTION WITH YOUR USE OR INABILITY TO USE THIS WEBSITE.

The laws of the State of California shall govern all matters relating to this website Privacy Policy, without giving effect to any principles of conflict of law.
